遠鑒字幕組製作
[Visionary] 0day-sub
翻譯&校對：william2568
「只有光靈可以控制魔杖的力量」
——《偉大預言 第7章第15節》
(豬頭)
(神創造萬物 眾生平等 但精靈最平等)
(獸人為你們奮戰 有誰為我們而戰?)
(信魔法必死)
(注意)
(魔君)
(獸人本色)
(消滅妖精)
(吉拉克永生)
(精靈扶持人類 只為壓迫獸人)
(獸人滾蛋!)
(自拍)
(洛杉磯警察)
(保釋貸款 我們懂獸人語 無需按金抵押)
(魔君定會歸來)
(洛杉磯 注意)
（１０東向- 洛杉磯４０５南向
- 精靈區）
(只限精靈)
(光明之盾)
(詛咒警察)
早安
Morning.
沃德
Ward.
要紅醬還是綠醬?
Red sauce? Green sauce?
寶貝 起床了麼?
Babe, you up?
已經下午了 起床啦
It's after noon, you gotta get up.
我泡了咖啡 來吧
I made some coffee, come on.
終於來了
There he is.
- 早安
- 是下午安
- Morning. - Afternoon.
- 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
嗨
Hi.
- 咖啡給我
- 知道了
- Coffee. - I know.
- 這堶惇O什麼
What the hell's this in my...
- 什麼東西？
- 怎麼了？
- What's that shit in there? - What?
我的天
- Whoops. - Yeah
咖啡濾紙用光了 我只好用餐巾
Ran out of coffee filters, had to use a napkin.
- 沒事的  我嚼乾淨好了
- It'll be fine. - I'll just chew that up next time.
拜託
Oh, come on.
怎麼又有妖精飛到喂鳥器堣F?
Why is the Fairy in the bird feeder again?
你說過已經殺掉了
- I...I thought...- You told methat you killed it.
好吧 我跟你說實話
All right, I'm gonna be honest with you. All right?
- 請說
- 我不惹妖精
- Please. - I don't fuck with no Fairies.
你要去惹惹外面的那只妖精
You need to fuck with that one.
小時候 我表哥戴戴 拿石頭扔妖精
When I was little, my cousin DayDay was throwing rocks at this Fairy.
那妖精把屎拉在自己手掌
- The Fairy shit in his own hand... - Uh-huh.
然後把屎扔到戴戴的眼睛堨h了
...threw the shit, and it went in DayDay's eye,
他的眼睛腫得跟哈蜜瓜一樣大
and it was like a fucking cantaloupe.
- 你在胡扯
- 他差點瞎了
- Bullshit story. - No, he almost lost his eye.
- 是真的
- 才怪
- I'm telling you. Listen... - That's not true.
讓趕走蜜蜂那個人來處理好了 兩百塊搞定
$200. Pay the man. Same man that does the bees.
我才不要花兩百塊
No, I'm not paying $200.
我眼前就有個高大猛男
I got this big, handsome, strapping man standing right in front of me.
去殺掉那只妖精 多謝您了
Go kill that Fairy, please. Thank you so much.
我去殺吧 先讓我喝完咖啡
I'll kill the Fairy. Let me finish my coffee.
- 好吧
- 好
- I'mma kill the Fairy. All right? - Okay.
喝完可能會死 你還是弄完再喝好了
That may kill you. You should do it before you finish the coffee.
工作怎樣？
- How was work? - Eh, work. Work is good,you know?
還好 挺好的 你聽說了麼 最近很多人挨刀子
Just, a lot of stab wounds lately. There's, uh...
今天 有個流浪漢進來 到處亂扔東西
We had this homeless guy come in, throwing equipment everywhere.
搞得一團糟
It was wild.
很多交通意外
A lot of traffic accidents,
- 有個老頭死掉了
- 不是有個獸人警察嗎？
- and this older guy, he coded out on me. - What about that cop that's an Orc
洛杉磯警局那個?
that's now on the LAPD force?
- 他又怎麼算？
- 他沒受過血禮
- How does that work? - He's not blooded.
他不屬於任何氏族
He's not part of any blooded clan.
對我們來說 他就像斷掉的手指一樣
He's like a finger that got cut off the hand.
我們就當他死了
He's dead to us.
簡直譁眾取寵
This is shock trauma at its finest.
然後你看那些人類 還有精靈
...and then you see the humans and the Elves...
我也不想跟他坐同一輛車
I don't want this guy in my car either.
親愛的 我不想你再挨槍子了
Baby, I don't want you to get shot again.
再過五年 我就能退休了
Five years, I'm gonna retire.
但…我得拿到我的養老金
But... I can't fuck up my pension.
那是我最擔心的
All right? I mean, that's my fucking worst nightmare.
你知道我最擔心什麼嗎?
You know what my worst nightmare is?
我擔心我上班的時候 有人把病床上或者輪椅上的你送到我面前
It's them wheeling you in when I'm at work.
那是我最擔心的
That's my nightmare.
過來親一個
Come on. Come here.
快去殺了那妖精
Fairy. Now.
看 我的警察鄰居來了
Hey, y'all, I want y'all to trip off my police-ass neighbor. He's a trip.
- 警官下午好
- 麥克你好啊
- Good afternoon, Officer. - Hey. What up, Mike?
那妖精在我家到處亂搞
Yo, that Fairy been all up in my crib,
還吃我的狗食
eating up my dog food and shit.
我剛要打電話給市政府呢
I'm about to call the city, man.
我代表的就是市政府
I am the city.
你的電話費省著
All right? You save your dime.
今天妖精的命 算個屁
Fairy lives don't matter today.
大家看著啊 有好戲了
Check this out, y'all. This is probably gonna be good.
開打了
It's on now!
上啊
Ring the bell, y'all.
挺溜的 你看這黑鬼
Damn. Look at this nigga, man.
就是這樣
Oh, that's it right there.
幹掉他 拿出你警察的樣子來
Oh, you got it now. Take the homie out LAPD-style like you do.
沒必要那麼狠吧 媽的
You ain't gotta do him like that. Damn!
真是慘不忍睹
That was nasty.
- 拜託
- 別這樣兄弟
- Man. - Come on, G.
- 我就是這麼做事的
- 媽的
- It's what I do. - Oh, shit.
你們繼續當你們的小混混
Oh, and, uh, you keep doing all your gangsta stuff.
我只是想把房子給賣了 不用擔心
I'm just trying to sell my house. Don't worry about that.
謝謝你表演 警官
Thanks for the show, Officer.
那個混蛋真是個瘋子 他老婆挺性感的
He's a trip. That motherfucker's crazy. Got a fine-ass wife, too.
你有麻煩了麼?
Are you in trouble?
有麻煩了? 你媽說了什麼?
Am I in trouble? What your mother say to you?
媽媽說尼克讓你惹上麻煩了 因為獸人都是笨蛋
Mom said that Nick got you in trouble because Orcs are dumb.
她說的不對 獸人不是笨蛋
That's not true, all right? Orcs are not dumb.
只是每個種族都各有不同啦
Just, uh... All of the races are-are different. Okay?
各種族之間的不同 不代表哪個種族就比較聰明
And just 'cause they're different doesn't mean anybody's smarter
或者哪個比較笨什麼的
or dumber, you know,
沒有誰比誰好的
better or worse than anybody.
行嗎? 只是...
All right? It's just-just...
大家只是想要和諧共處 然後...
You know, everybody's just trying to get along and-and...
過好日子
have a good life.
什麼情況
What the hell?
寶貝 你去穿好衣服 穿好衣服
Hey, baby, you gotta take some clothes. Get some clothes.
知道了
Fine.
嘿
Hey, hey!
嘿 搭檔
Hey, partner.
準備好復工了嗎? 傷勢都好了?
Ready to get back to work? All healed up?
你來我家幹嘛?
What the hell are you doing at my house?
你幹嘛來這? 還站在我家的草坪上?
Why are you at my house? Why are you on my lawn?
你的草坪早死光了
Your lawn's dead, Ward.
沒錯 所以我才在這播種了
Exactly. Which is why I seeded it
然後灑滿牛糞 讓草長回來
and spread cow shit everywhere so it grows back.
那才不是牛糞
That's not really cow shit.
- 什麼意思？
- 明明是下水道堛瑭T便
- What do you mean it's not cow shit? - It's sewage, from toilets.
從污水處理廠找來的 肯定是這樣
From the treatment plant, swear to God.
我花了四百塊買回來的
I paid $400 for this.
- 是牛屎
- 是人的屎
- That's bullshit. - Human shit.
- 你以為我是來這跟你談化肥的？
- 算了
- Why do you think I compost? - Whatever. Whatever. Whatever.
以後你都不准再來我家了
You don't ever come here in that ever again.
我剛去進行多元化培訓 準備去酒吧 剛好經過你家 我以為
I was at diversity training. Your house is on the way to the bar. I thought...
- 嗨尼克
- 蘇菲雅你好嗎大明星？
- Hi, Nick. - Hey, Sophia. What's up, rock star?
我們要去奶奶家
We're gonna go to Grandma's.
- 去奶奶家？上車我們送你去
- 別扯了
- Grandma's? Hop in, we'll give you a ride. - Shut up.
- 這又不是出租車
- 別叫尼克閉嘴
- This ain't no Uber, man. - Don't tell Nick to shut up.
他也是個人啦
He's a person, too.
謝謝你 親愛的
Oh, thank you, sweetie.
你女兒還真懂事
That's an enlightened kid you got there, Daryl.
別管我
Don't worry about me.
繼續搞你們的燒烤
Just Crip-walk your asses on back to the barbecue.
我只是想載你一程...
Be nice to give you a ride...
- 閉嘴
- ．．．你第一天復工呢
- Shut up. - ...on your first day back.
這歌很好聽
Lovely song.
外婆家到了
There's Grandma.
我...
Hey. Uh, I'm...
好 能見到你真好
Okay. Good to see you.
寶貝 怎麼了?
All right, baby. What's up?
怎麼了? 你怎麼悶悶不樂的?
What's happening? What's up? Why you sad?
怎麼了?
What happened?
我不想你死掉
I don't want you to die.
我不會死啦 怎麼了?
I'm not gonna die. What are you...
- 我怎麼會死？
- 媽媽說尼克會把你害死
- What you talking about? - Mama said Nick's gonna get you killed.
她怎麼會說那種話?
I don't know why she said...
尼克不會害死我啦
Nick is not gonna get me killed, all right?
你為什麼要當警察?
Why do you have to be a policeman?
大家都討厭警察
Everybody hates policemen.
嘿
Hey...
你聞起來好像挺久沒睡覺了
Know what? You smell like you haven't slept.
我的工作包埵鹵げ簪 你晚上睡前吃一顆
I have melatonin in my war bag. You take one before bed,
- 關掉筆記本然後．．
- 也許我晚上會睡不著
- turn off the laptop, get... - Maybe I'm having trouble sleeping
是因為我經常做噩夢
because of the nightmares I'm having
夢見有人用散彈鎗轟我
from being blasted across the street with a shotgun
而你跑去買卷餅了
while your ass was getting a burrito.
我是要買卷餅給你吃啊
But I was getting a burrito for you.
- 對啊
- 我不吃牛肉的
- Yeah... - I don't eat cow flesh.
你覺得 你去買卷餅的時候
Do you think that you could get a burrito
能同時做好工作嗎?
and do your job?
你覺得 你可以像個人類警察那樣
You think you could get a burrito and watch my back
- 邊買卷餅邊保護好我嗎？
- 可以
- like every other cop manages to do? - Yes.
我知道 你對我失望
Look, I know... you're disappointed in me.
我知道你覺得我沒做好工作 讓你失望了
I know that you think that I let you down.
- 但是你知道嗎？
- 我．．．
- Yeah. You know what? - But I...
新的一天了
You know what? It's a new day.
回去報到後 我們就重頭開始
Back to work. We hitting the reset button.
知道 重頭開始
Copy that. Copy that. We're hitting the reset button.
咱們一起邁步向前
Moving forward together.
咱倆是朋友 並肩作戰
As friends, together.
我們以後不聽獸人音樂了
We will not be listening to no Orkish music.
這是史上最棒的情歌之一
That is one of the greatest love songs ever written.
那是監獄媔ヶ菄滷◇q吧
That's a love song in prison.
我覺得你缺愛了 沃德
I believe that you're lacking in love, Ward.
- 你說什麼？
- 我說的愛．．．
- I'm what? - By love, I mean...
我是說肉體上的愛
like... physical love.
對哦
Yeah. Um...
是吧?
Right?
我是直男 我才不需要那種愛 我挺好的
I'm straight. I don't need no physical love. Trust me, I'm good.
你掩蓋不了的 沃德
You can't hide it, Ward.
人類會顯示出一些外部特徵
Humans have physical tells.
- 特徵？
- 對啊
- Tells, huh? - Yeah.
- 都在你的臉上寫著呢
- 我現在面無表情
- It's called a face. - I ain't making no face.
- 你現在就挺有表情的
- 根本沒有任何表情
- Like the face you're making right now. - I ain't making no face.
行吧
All right.
我現在是什麼表情?
What face am I making?
一副"慾求不滿的人類"的表情
"A human who needs a lot more conjugal love" type face.
"慾求不滿"的表情? 所以你很瞭解人類的表情
"Conjugal love" face. So you know human face...
再來一個 人類還有什麼表情?
Show me another human face.
- 人類還有什麼表情
- 額．．
- What's another one we make? - Oh, uh...
- 那是什麼表情？
- 人類煎餅不夠吃了就是這樣的表情
- What's that face? - Human who doesn't get anymore pancakes.
- 人類確實很喜歡吃煎餅
- 我還能學很多表情呢
- We do like our pancakes, for real. - I got a lot of 'em.
- 還有很多？
- 確實有很多
- You got a lot? - I got a lot of them.
給我看看一個獸人把嘴閉起來
Show me the face an Orc makes when he just shut the fuck up,
不說話 開車去上班的表情
and don't say shit, and just drive to work.
沒錯 就是這樣!你演得很好
Yeah, that's it! That's it! Oh, you got that one!
真是惟妙惟肖啊
Yeah, you killing that one.
你應該多做那個表情 保持下去就好
You should do that one. Do that one, like, all the time.
你走這邊幹嘛?
Whoa. Whoa. Why you going this way?
沒事 我們這是抄近路
It's fine, it's a shortcut.
這人的人很好的
See? They're very nice here.
夥計 你不能開車經過精靈區啊
Dude, you can't go through Elftown.
你這是要害死我啊 夥計
You are killing me. Killing me, dude.
你是要幹嘛? 去買名牌鞋子嗎?
So, what, you trying to... get yourself some designer shoes?
這堻ㄛO超有錢的精靈
Ain't nothing over here but rich-ass Elves
操控世界 一直在瘋狂購物
just running the world and shopping.
我最討厭精靈區了
I hate Elftown.
連司機都瞧不起人
Even the chauffeurs are snobs.
沃德 這麼快就回來了?
Hey. Back already, Ward?
跟你同車的那個外族獸人呢?
Where's the, uh, diversity hire you ride with?
你跟雅各比是什麼搭檔? 跳舞的舞伴嗎?
Yeah, what kind of partner is Jakoby? Is he your dance partner?
是炮友嗎?
Your sexual partner?
我覺得他抓壞人方面不怎麼在行
'Cause he fucking sucks at catching bad guys.
那是氏族法規
That's Clan Law shit, dog.
獸人得互相照應的
Orcs got each other's backs.
你們怎麼說得好像是我特意選他做我的搭檔?
Hey, look, why y'all acting like I put this dude in my car?
所以你打算要怎樣把他趕走?
So what are you doing to get him the fuck out of this division, my friend?
要是他能幹好工作的話 我沒什麼辦法趕他走
Hey, long as he pull his weight, I ain't got no beef with him.
你可以想想辦法啊
No. No, no, no. You could do shit, man.
寫封信之類的 我們配合你 他就死定了
You could write a letter. His ass would be gone if we back you up.
肯定沒錯
That's a fact.
- 沃德你不在乎就算了
- 嗯
- But you only care about yourself, Ward. - Right.
我也沒有徵求你的建議啊
Did I... Did I ask you for advice?
我大概等到第九次離婚的時候 再問問你的意見
'Cause I'll probably wait till I'm on my, like, ninth divorce,
到時候你的建議 大概會很有用
then your advice will come in really handy.
好啊 真他媽好 我會記住
That's good. That's fucking good. Noted.
那個獸人混蛋 依然逍遙法外
Meanwhile, that Orc fuck is still out there
就因為雅各比 更看重氏族血統 而不是他的警徽
because Jakoby chose clan blood over the badge.
可能那個嫌犯只是逃走了而已
Or the motherfucker just got away.
雅各比放他走了 他才逃得掉
He got away 'cause Jakoby let him.
然後呢?
What happens next?
要是這個臭豬頭
What happens the next time this pig motherfucker
再找警察下手呢？
makes a cop suck-start his fucking 12-gauge?
萬一倒霉的是布朗
Only this time, it's Brown,
或者是希克斯 或者是我呢?
or it's Hicks, or it's fucking me.
那時候你會怎麼想 沃德? 到時候你可就要負責了
How you gonna feel, Ward? 'Cause that shit is on you.
如果是你的話 我大概...
Well, if you in the box, I'll probably be like...
沃德 你這個狗娘養的
Ward, you son of a bitch.
聽著 他跟我同車
Hey, look, I got a dude in my car,
全世界都盯著我們看呢
the whole world is watching, all right?
我沒有主動要求跟他同車 我不想這樣 但沒有人徵求過我的意見
I didn't ask for it, I don't want it, but I don't get a vote.
要是上頭僱用更多的獸人怎麼辦? 他們都說
And what happens if they hire more? You know what they say.
跟隨過魔君的 永遠都是魔君的爪牙
Once with the Dark Lord, always with the Dark Lord.
他們選擇邪惡的一方
They chose evil.
我就不明白了
Here's the thing I can't understand.
你們這群笨蛋 連自己孩子媽媽的生日都記不清楚
How do a bunch of dudes who can barely remember their baby mama's birthday
怎麼會對兩千年前的事情念念不忘
have beef with a whole race
就因為這屁事仇視一整個種族?
over some shit that happened 2,000 years ago?
你聽好了 夥計
Here's the fucking deal, man.
你他們的讓雅各比離我遠點
You keep Jakoby the fuck away from me. Okay?
逼急了我會把這獸人給斃了 我他媽的天不怕地不怕
I'll drop an Orc. I don't give a fuck.
我祖先在俄羅斯 宰殺過數以千計的獸人
My ancestors killed them by the fucking thousands in Russia.
歡迎沃德回歸崗位
- Attaboy, Ward! - About time, Ward.
好了 大家安靜 隊長來了
All right, settle down, settle down. The captain's coming.
沃德 我給你留了位子
Ward, I saved you a seat.
有請隊長發言
Take it away, boss.
沃德 歡迎你回來
Ward, nice to see you back.
隊長好
Cap.
- 今天晚上有三重危機
- 嘿這是你表親嗎？
- Tonight's the trifecta. - Hey, is that your cousin?
今天有滿月 星期五
Full moon, Friday night...
- 不是
- 還有熱浪
- No. - ...summer heat wave.
所以你們接到任務要盡快處理
That means: clear your calls fast,
然後同事間相互幫助
help your colleagues clear theirs,
在我本次負責期間 避免再發生謀殺案
get me out of this deployment period without another murder,
事成後我請各位喝咖啡
I'll buy you all coffee.
接下來由程警長介紹情況
Sergeant Ching, all yours.
聽到名字之後 過來領佩槍和對講機 然後出發去巡邏
All right, after I call your name, get your shotguns and radios and deploy.
除非有壞人殺到警局來了 否則別讓我看到你們呆在這
I don't want to see you here unless there's bad guys under the desks.
３Ｍ２５伯拉德
Three-Mary-25, Pollard.
３Ｍ５５金
Three-Mary-55, Kim.
３Ｍ６０湯瑪斯
Three-Mary-60, Thomas.
３Ａ２１佩朋跟格斯
Three-A-21, Pippen and Gosser.
３Ａ５４漢考克跟韋勒
Three-A-54, Hancock and Wheeler.
３Ａ８０克勞福跟鄧肯
Three-A-80, Crawford and Duncan.
３Ａ９雅各比跟沃德
Three-A-9, Jakoby and Ward.
- ３Ａ３４瓊斯跟莫連戈
- 你先去裝備室
- Three-A-34, Jones and Morengo. - Hey, uh, hit the kit room.
- ３Ａ８２奧提茲跟曼斯亞
- 我在加油站跟你會合
- Three-A-82, Ortiz and Mencia... - I'll meet you at the gas pumps.
- 我很快就過去我先要．．
- 好
- I'll be right down. I just need to... - Okay.
3A99...
Three-A-99...
- 不行
- 有什麼不行的把他調去別車
- No. - Yes. Put him in another car.
看我這樣子 你覺得
What the fuck about my demeanor gives you the impression
我有興趣完成局堛疑~人種族多樣性目標?
that I want to be a target on the department's Orc-diversity radar?
這是高層做的決定
These decisions are made nine miles above me.
不是 這安排表白紙黑字 就在你眼前啊
No. They're made right on your paper, right there.
把他劃掉
Scratch him out.
劃掉他的名字 再寫一個 隨便誰都行
Scratch his name out. Put another name, anybody.
沃德 其他人都不願意跟你同車
Ward, no one wants to ride with you.
再見 別再中槍了
Goodbye. Don't get shot again.
祝你好運
Good luck.
- 很不錯嘛
- 看上去挺好的
- Hey, looking good, bud. - Looking real good. Real good.
各位小心
Be safe, guys.
兄弟們 你們好啊
What's up, homies?
你還沒死?
Your ass still alive?
你覺得我會死?
You know something about that?
不是我幹的
It wasn't me.
別再街上閒晃
Get the fuck off of the street or I'mma call your PO,
否則我打給你的保釋官 說你跟你的混混兄弟們喝酒
tell him you out drinking with the homies.
別讓我一句話說兩次
I ain't gonna tell you two times.
我們走吧
Let's go.
如果跟這些霧牙幫的混蛋開打
I need to know if the shit pop off with these Fogteeth fools
你得保護我 你是個警察 這點比你是獸人更重要
that you got my back, that you a cop first.
明白了麼?
Are we clear?
明白
Clear.
我管的是毒品 錢和槍械 那是我的工作
I'm about dope, money, and guns. That's my job.
你的工作是保證我的安全 讓我晚上能平安回家
Your job is to make sure I go home at night.
- 我不喜歡這種閒聊
- 這不是閒聊
- I don't like this small talk. - This ain't no small talk.
這重要的很
This is big-ass talk.
我們可是要面對真槍實彈的
We doing real shit out here.
西湖區所有小隊３Ａ４小隊請求增援
All Westlake units, three-A-4 is requesting assistance.
請火速前往第六街與懷特莫街交叉口
Sixth and Whitmore. Sixth and Whitmore.
西湖區所有小隊３Ａ４小隊請求增援
All Westlake units, Three-A-4...
把他壓在地上!
Get him the fuck on the ground!
趴在車上
Back the fuck up!
別動 他媽的別動
Stay there! Stay right fucking there!
- 別亂動
- 閉嘴
- Do not resist! Don't... - Shut the fuck up!
我得問清楚 你到底是警察的身份優先
I need to know if you're a cop first...
還是獸人的身份優先
or an Orc first.
- 我要聽你說出來
- 沃德
- I need to hear you say it. - Ward, I...
我自小就想當一名警察
I wanted to be a cop since I was a little kid.
警察是我唯一的身份
I am nothing else.
這枚警徽對我來說 比空氣還重要
My badge means more to me than the air I breathe.
你用不著質疑我
So don't question me.
３Ａ９第五街西湖區有騷擾事故
Three-A-9, 415. Fifth and Westlake.
二級事態 事件編號2415
Code two, incident 2415.
３Ａ９收到我們在路上
Three-Adam-9. Roger, show us en route.
明白３Ａ９
Three-A-9, roger.
我們走吧
The fuck outta here.
我的天
God damn it!
羅德古茲 嘿
Rodriguez. Hey.
媽的 還以為你死了
Oh, shit, man. I thought you were dead.
我還有很多賬單要付 死不了
Nah, man, too many bills to pay.
我懂
I hear ya.
我還以為你在放第八千次產假呢
I thought you were out having your, like, zillionth baby.
不是啦 比計劃生產時間晚了一星期 我們下周給她人工催產
Ah, nah, man. Marisol's a week late. We're inducing next week, though.
第五胎呢
Number five.
- 五個哦
- 要養活五個孩子呢
- Five. - Lot of mouths to feed.
是啊 兄弟
Yeah, man.
先生...
Sir...
請把劍放下
drop the sword.
你
You.
九族聯軍並肩作戰
The Army of Nine Races fought shoulder to shoulder
保護著你忽視的世界
to give you the world you neglect.
- 讓他閉嘴
- 兩千年前
- Hey, tell him to shut up. - 2,000 years ago,
- 我們用刀劍和弓箭作戰
- 先生
- we fought them with swords and arrows. - Sir...
現在魔君歸來 收復獸人的心
And now, the Dark One returns to reclaim Orc hearts!
怎麼我去哪 他們都說獸人都是壞蛋?
Everywhere I go, why have Orcs always gotta be the bad guys?
別說了 現在還有人 拿阿拉摩之戰找墨西哥人的麻煩呢
Hey, don't look at me, man. Mexicans still get shit for the Alamo.
別過來!退後!
Get back! Get back!
先生 要是你不想死的話 就他媽的馬上把劍丟掉!
Sir, unless you wanna die, you drop that sword right fucking now!
你害我中過槍 別讓我被捅了
Hey, you got me shot, don't get me stabbed.
轉過身去 先生
Turn around, sir.
- 雙手放在頭頂
- 我現在就放我的天
- Hands on your head. - I'm doing it, man. Jeez.
- 跪在地上
- 行我跪下
- On your knees. - I... All right.
別動
Don't move.
我只是隨便耍耍刀而已
Having a little fun.
該死的
Aah! Shit!
行了 媽的
All right. Damn.
我又沒有反抗
I'm not resisting, man.
３Ａ９小隊報告拘捕了一人
Three-Adam-9, one in custody.
各小隊注意 第五街西湖區疑犯已被拘捕
All units, code four. Fifth and Westlake, suspect in custody.
夥計 輕一點
Okay, man, easy. Gimme a... Gimme a... Ow!
- 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
跟你說一下
Real quick.
收到了一些關於幫派的情報 說霧牙幫鬧得很厲害
Gang intel said Fogteeth's been smashing like a motherfucker,
阿爾塔米拉幫也是目無王法
and Altamira's gangbanging like it's 1999.
- 你們小心點
- 你也是
- Watch your backs out there. - Hey, you too.
- 沒問題
- 多和你的家人待一會
- All right, brother. - Kiss your family.
先生 你可以靠後一點麼
Sir, can you sit back?
你身上挺臭的 可以坐後一點嗎?
You-You stink like shit. Can you sit back?
謝謝
Thank you.
我的天
Come on.
糟透了
That's bad.
我有一條來自光明之盾的訊息
I have a message from the Shield of Light.
不要忘記過去
Remember the old ways.
別忘記你的身份
Remember what you are.
那是獸人語嗎?
Is that Orkish?
你怎麼會說獸人語?
How the hell do you know how to speak Orkish?
他說什麼?
What'd he say?
不要忘記你的傳統
Remember your traditions.
只有氏族的法則能拯救你
Only clan ways can save you.
預言已經選中了你
The Prophecy has chosen you.
跟你一起的那個人受到了祝福
The man with you is blessed.
雅各比!
Jakoby!
小心點 兄弟
Come on, man.
你到底是怎麼了? 他說了什麼?
What the hell is your problem? What'd he say?
他在胡說八道
He's not making any sense.
雅各比在哪?
Where's Jakoby?
在記錄我們逮捕的犯人
Uh, booking our body, ma'am.
我很喜歡你的髮型
Um, I love your hair.
你是哪位?
Who are you?
我可以解雇你 或者送你去坐牢
I'm the unemployment line, or a prison sentence.
我也可以是救贖你的天使 你的命運掌握在自己手上 夥計
I could be the Angel of Mercy, but it's up to you, buddy.
內務部
Internal Affairs.
沒錯 來找你好幾次了 我們來回顧一下案情
That's right, all fucking day long. Now, let's review, kids.
有個豬頭混蛋 用霰彈槍擊中你的防彈衣
Some pigskin piece of shit puts a load of buckshot into your trauma plate.
那個混帳徒步逃走雅各比去追捕．．．
- Shithead foot-bails, Jakoby pursues... - Hey!
嘿
Hey!
警察 別跑!
Police! Stop!
然後把犯人追到了一個死胡同?
...corners his asshole in, what, a dead-end alley?
雅各比聲稱和疑犯扭打在一起 他的武器掉在地上
Jakoby states dude tackled and disarmed him.
然後跳上放火梯 逃離追捕
Then jumped on a fire escape ladder and evaded arrest.
這是雅各比簽名的口供
Jakoby's signed statement.
我們測量過了 那條梯子離地有4米高
Ladder's 13 feet off the ground. We measured.
沒有獸人能跳那麼高
- No Orc has a six-foot vertical.
也許疑犯身手很好 長官
Perhaps the suspect was light on his feet, sir.
獸人懂輕功嗎?
Do Orcs have, uh, mad hops?
有多少獸人打籃球?
How many Orcs are ballers?
- 什麼意思？
- 你聽到他說的話了
- Excuse me? - You fuckin' heard the detective.
- 有多少獸人打職業籃球？
- 沒有
- How many Orcs play pro basketball? - None.
他們行動緩慢 很笨拙
They're slow, they're heavy.
所以職業足球 有一半的防守線鋒都是獸人
That's why half the NFL defensive lines are Orkish.
這不是種族歧視 是物理定律
It's not racism, it's physics.
肯定是雅各比放走了 拿槍轟你的那個豬頭混蛋
Jakoby kicked loose that pigskin fuck who blasted you.
你自己想想
Do the math.
在獸人眼中 氏族法規高於一切 那是事實
Orcs hold Clan Law above all else. That's a fact.
雅各比的事非常敏感 全世界都在看
The Jakoby issue is sensitive. The world's watching.
- 我們不能無緣無故就解雇他
- 所以．．．
- We can't fire him without cause. - Which is why...
你要讓他認罪
you're gonna get him to admit it...
而且要錄音
and you're gonna record him.
走開啦
The fuck outta here.
我也不想跟他同車
I want the guy out of my car, but...
要是我告密的話 我巡警就混不下去了
I snitch, I'm done as a street cop.
我們知道你還不起房貸
We know, uh, you got a house note you can't pay down.
對吧? 債台高築
Right? Drowning in debt.
還有一個女兒 你都要養不起了
Raising a little girl you can't afford to pay for.
還真是他們的模範父親
Father of the fucking year.
你再提起我的家人 我就把你的頭劈成兩半
You talk about my family again, I'll split your fucking head open.
沃德
Ward.
你要保住這份工作
You need this job.
別為了雅各比 放棄這一切
Don't throw it away for Jakoby.
別碰我
Get off me. Get off me.
錄音筆給我
Give it to me.
我不出庭作證
No testifying...
不會作供
no depositions,
也不寫報告
no paperwork.
沒問題
Good man.
很識相
Very smart.
把你的小鬍子剃掉 混蛋
Shave your mustache, bitch.
公事公辦而已
It's just business.
這個地方一團糟
Place is a shithole.
獸人還戴警章
An Orc with a badge.
真是難以置信
Incredible.
這種事可不常見 就像精靈拿著拖把
That's some shit you don't see every day. Like an Elf with a mop.
你看到他們嗎?
Did you see those two guys?
他們好像是聯邦探員 是來找我麻煩的嗎?
I think they're feds. Could they be here for me?
聯邦探員才不在乎 洛杉磯的獸人社區呢
Feds don't give a shit about the LA Orc community.
你說的也對
Yeah, you're right.
我女兒...
S... So, my-my daughter...
蘇菲雅
Sophia...
她常常做一些不該做的事情
she be doing shit all the time, man, that she don't have no business doing.
但她很誠實
But... she comes clean.
每次都會說實話
She always tells the truth.
因為知道 說實話是很好的
'Cause she realized it feels good.
她好我也好
Feels good to her, feels good to me.
有時候
And, uh, truth just has a way...
真相能掃除兩個人之間的陰霾
of clearing the air between people.
可以讓一些事情更明瞭 你懂嗎?
If it cleanses... cleanses some shit, you know,
所以說實話就行了
it's like, just tell the truth.
我知道局埵酗@些很不好的事情
I know something very bad happened at the station.
我知道的
I know.
所以你打算告訴我麼?
So are you gonna tell me about it or no?
我是在說你的事情
I'm talking about you. All right?
你不用迴避話題 警局沒事發...
Don't be trying to twist this. Nothing happened at the...
- 我沒有迴避．．．
- 亞布罕街３４１號有不明騷動
- I'm not... - ...trouble, 341 Abrams.
事件編號2815
Code two, incident 2815.
３Ａ９小隊報告我們在路上
Three-Adam-9, show us en route.
去亞布罕街341號
341 Abrams.
３Ａ９明白
Three-A-9, roger.
你加入光明之盾組織有多久了?
How long you been in Shield of Light?
那是什麼東西?
What's that?
天
God!
你個小混帳
You little fuck-up.
該死的!你在幹嘛?
Aah! Shit! What are you doing, man?
別發問 給我閉嘴
No questions, just shut up.
這個光明之盾紋身不錯啊
Hey, nice Shield of Light tattoo!
- 真不錯啊
- 知道我們是誰嗎？
- Good one. - You know who we are?
打掃房間的
Housekeeping.
你看看這個
You might wanna look at this.
該死的 魔法調查隊
Fuck. Magic Task Force.
對 我們是魔法聯邦探員
Right. The magic feds.
沙堮 要是你繼續耍小聰明
You know, Serling, if you're gonna play stupid games,
下場會很慘
you're gonna win stupid prizes.
去死吧
Fuck you.
混蛋 你再惹我試試?
You wanna test me, asshole?
好了 我不是你的敵人
Okay! I'm not your enemy, man.
你瞭解煉獄黨的情況麼
What do you know about the Inferni?
他們是精靈
Um... they're Elves.
是叛亂的精靈
Renegade Elves.
叛亂精靈 不好意思
Renegade Elves, sorry.
因為精靈們都超棒的 對吧?
Because Elves are awesome, right?
他們要讓魔君復活
They're gonna bring back the Dark Lord.
天方夜譚
Fairy fucking tales.
他們打算怎麼讓他復活?
How do they plan to do that?
他們獲得三根魔杖 就能讓他死而復生
When they get three Magic Wands, they can raise him from the dead.
你認得這個人嗎?
You recognize her?
那是莉拉
That's Leilah.
她是煉獄黨的頭目
She's an Inferni coven leader.
她是個光靈
She's a Bright.
你有沒有注意到到大部分的光靈都是精靈
You ever notice how most Brights are Elves,
然後整個世界都是精靈說了算嗎?
and Elves run the world?
是巧合嗎?
Coincidence?
光靈中也有人類
There are human Brights.
一百萬個人類中才有一個吧
One in a million.
你知道怎樣才能判別一個人是不是光靈麼?
But you know how you know if you're a Bright?
光靈能徒手
When you touch a Wand...
觸碰魔杖
with your bare hand...
還不會把自己炸死
and don't explode.
你會去試試麼?
Would you do that?
為了發現真相 你願意拿自己的命去冒險嗎?
Would you die to learn the truth about yourself?
要是我有魔杖的話 我會試試
If I had a Wand... I'd try.
我們言歸正傳
Let's get back on track.
所以莉拉手上有一根魔杖 然後她在追殺媞卡 對吧?
So Leilah has a Magic Wand, and she's coming after Tikka, right?
她寧可把整個城市鬧個底朝天 也要達成自己的目標
And she'll shred this city to do it.
我們只要找到媞卡 就能設陷阱抓獲莉拉
We get Tikka, we can set a trap for Leilah.
我們要找到魔杖 追捕光靈
We hunt Wands, we hunt Brights.
我們就是幹這行的 而且我們挺擅長幹這個的
That's what we do, and we're pretty fucking good at it.
你要不要幫助我們?
You wanna help us?
不了吧
Come on.
魔君要歸來了
The Dark Lord's coming.
你們要怎麼跟他鬥? 開坦克?
What, are you gonna to fight him with, with tanks?
拿無人機炸他?
Huh? You gonna drone him?
兩千年前 魔法的力量阻止了他
Two thousand years ago, magic stopped him.
只有魔法能再次擊倒他
And magic will stop him again.
總有一天 你們會乞求我們幫忙
One day, you all are gonna come begging for our help.
我們會阻止魔君的
And we'll be there. We'll stop him.
光明之盾會阻止他
The Shield of Light will stop him.
說完了
I'm done.
我們說完了
We're done.
如果你跟我作對
If you act like my enemy...
你就是我的敵人
you become my enemy.
看到了麼?
See that?
是個把風的
- Oh, it's a spotter. - Mm-hmm.
趴下 找掩護
Get down! Down! Go!
這可不太妙
Oh. Yeah, that's... That's not good.
我們可能會死
- Yeah. - We could die.
- 第一次有人朝你開槍？
- 對
- First time being shot at? - Yeah.
不得不說 這挺不妙的
I have to say, I dislike it very much.
對 糟透了
Yeah, it fucking sucks.
聽著 數三聲 我們就反擊
All right, look... on three, we're gonna dump this asshole.
行嗎?
All right?
- 很合理
- 我們使用武力
- Right. That makes sense. - Use force.
- 好的
- 行
- All right. - Yeah.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
- 你還好嗎？
- 還好
- You all right? - Hmm? Yeah.
身上沒多幾個洞吧？
- No holes? - Huh? Uh...
身上只有生下來那幾個洞
Only the ones that I was born with.
你呢?
How are your holes?
你怎麼能讓槍戰的氣氛都變的這麼尷尬?
The fuck can you make a shootout awkward?
對不起
Sorry.
他得重新裝彈 知道嗎?
Wait for the reload! All right?
- 他早晚得重新裝彈
- 重新裝彈
- He's gonna have to reload. - Reload.
現在!
Now!
該死
Shit.
打死他了
We got him.
開門 去開門
Get the door. Get the door.
- 我們不等援軍嗎？
- 我們就是援軍
- Shouldn't we wait for the cavalry? - We are the cavalry.
沃德 我們可以等增援嗎? 沃德?
Ward, can't we wait for backup? Ward.
上...
Go, go, go.
我聞到血的味道 沃德
I smell blood, Ward.
很多血
Lots of blood.
- 那是什麼？
- 我不知道
- What's that? - Don't know.
該死的
Oh, shit.
- 屍體
- 什麼？
- Body. Body. - What?
該死
Shit. Shit.
- 去守住走道
Cover the hall.
- 那是什麼東西？
- 守住走道
- What the fuck is that? - Cover the hall.
好的
Okay.
該死的
Oh, shit.
什麼都不要碰
Don't touch anything.
好的
Yeah.
還有屍體
- Body. - Wh...?
槍手就是他 他死了
That's our shooter, he's down.
這堶掄晹酗H 我能嗅到
Someone's in here. I can smell them.
這些人死得好慘
These people died so bad.
安全
Clear.
這媯o生了怪事
Something unusual has happened here.
３Ａ９小隊報告這堿O亞布罕街３４１號
Three-Adam-9, 341 Abrams.
現場可能有光靈
Possible Bright at our location.
要求其他小隊增援 請魔法監督員到場
Request additional units and a supervisor.
我重複一遍 現場可能有魔法使用者
I repeat: Possible magic-user on scene.
別跑!
Hey! Freeze!
別動 不要跑!
You! Wait, stop!
嘿
Hey! Hey!
別跑!
Stop running!
別動！抓住她
- Hold her, hold her! - Stop! Stop! Stop!
她拿著什麼?
What has she got?
那是什麼?
What is that? What is that?
去找其他兄弟
Go get the homies.
把它放下 否則我打死你!
Put it down or I'm gonna shoot you in your face!
那是...?
Is that...?
是魔杖
It's a Magic Wand.
什麼...? 誰...?
Who, uh...
你是誰?
Who are you?
求你們保護我
Please protect me.
她在說精靈語
She's speaking Elvish.
我不懂精靈語
I don't speak Elvish.
我高中的時候學了兩年精靈語
Well, I took two years in high school, but, uh...
她說有人要來了
She said somebody's coming.
求你們保護我和魔杖
Please protect me and the Wand.
依我所見 有光靈來到這 使用了魔杖
As far as I can tell, a Bright came in, used the Wand, and...
用魔法把所有人弄成那樣
magicked everybody the fuck up. Uh...
我們要撤離這個區域 清空現場
We need to evacuate this neighborhood, secure the scene,
設立警戒線 等聯邦探員抵達
hold the perimeter till the feds get here.
你們他媽的在想什麼 都是新來的嗎?
What the fuck are you, new?
- 這情況我們處理不了
- 那是魔法
- This is way above our pay grade. - That's magic right there.
可以達成任何願望
That's whatever you want.
想要一百萬嗎?
You want a million dollars?
一千萬?
You want ten million?
想長高或者矮一點麼?
You wanna be taller or shorter?
想讓老二變大麼?
Make your dick bigger?
想回到過去 娶那個沒在高中舞會給你口交的女孩結婚麼?
You wanna go back in time, marry the girl who didn't blow you on prom night?
用這個就行
That's how you do it, right there.
顯然 我們的高中舞會沒你們那麼開放
Well, clearly, we had different prom nights.
但那是一根魔杖啊
But that is a Magic Wand,
你根本不懂怎麼用它
and you don't know how to use it.
亂來的話 只會害死我們
And you're gonna kill us all trying.
只有光靈能用魔杖 我看你就不像個巫師
Only a Bright can use a Wand, and you don't look like a wizard to me.
別碰那根魔杖
Don't put your hands on that Wand.
- 別碰它
- 我能搞定
- Hey, don't touch the Wand. - I got it.
別碰
Don't touch it.
嘿... 不要...
Hey, hey, hey. Don't be...
好涼啊
Fucking ice cold.
- 你不能把魔杖偷走
- 沒有人會來的沃德
- All right, you're not stealing that Wand. - Nobody's coming, Ward.
你們這是要幹嘛?
Fuck is you squaring off on, bitch?
警長 你得管好你的手下
Hey, Sarge, you need to talk to your boys right now.
你跟我們一樣 需要這根魔杖發家致富 也許比我們更需要
You need this just as much as we do, maybe more.
你的家人就靠你了 你不想幫他們嗎?
Your family depends on you. Don't you wanna be there for them?
那雅各比呢?
What about Jakoby?
你能告訴我 你的名字嗎?
Can you tell me your name?
- 媞卡
- Tikka. - Tikka.
我叫媞卡
My name is Tikka.
她要來了 我們要離開這
We have to leave before she comes.
誰要來?
Before who comes?
不能這樣
It's not happening.
不行
No. No.
伯拉德 他在猶豫
Pollard, he's spinning.
- 他根本沒猶豫的
- 他沒事
- No, he's not spinning worth shit. - He's fine, he's fine.
- 這不太妙
- 冷靜點
- This is stupid. - Calm down.
- 冷靜點他沒事的
- 別過來
- Hey, fucking chill. He's fine. - Back up.
- 他沒事
- 別他媽的碰我
- He's fin... Hey, hey! - The fuck you gonna do?
冷靜點 別亂來 退後
Calm down. Fucking calm down. Back the fuck up.
退後點 聽著
Back the fuck up. Listen. Listen.
我們事在必行
This is happening.
- 已經決定了
- 別碰我
- This is fucking happening. - Fuck off of me.
行嗎?
All right?
- 該死的
- 沒事
- Fuck. - It's okay.
沒事的
It's okay.
你走出這道門 你的人生軌跡就徹底改變了
There's no version of you walking out of here with life as you know it intact.
我不管了 我們拿走魔杖 殺了那個獸人
Fuck this. We are taking the Wand, and the Orc dies.
你現在必須做決定
And you got a big decision right now.
你是想讓自己女兒變成孤兒 然後雅各比再步你的後塵
Either your little girl grows up without a daddy and Jakoby dies,
還是只有雅各比死 你自己選吧
or just Jakoby dies. And it is time to make a choice.
你或他 沃德 你死還是他死
You or him, Ward. You or him.
明天的報紙會說什麼來著 有一個警察死在這 還是兩個?
Is tomorrow's LA Times gonna say one cop died here, or two?
看他這樣子 他明白我們的意思了
Yeah, there it is. He just caught up to it.
這真是皆大歡喜啊
Everyone wins.
咱們警局能擺脫雅各比 他死得風光 大眾也會高興
Department gets rid of Jakoby, he dies a hero, public's happy.
報告也不用多寫了
This report writes itself.
一切都很完美啊
The perfect storm, bro.
這麼完美的機會
It's the perfect storm.
你沒事吧?
You okay?
你帶上蘇菲雅 馬上離開城
Hey. Take Sophia, get out of town right now.
什麼? 怎麼了?
What? Why?
馬上出城去 我愛你
Get out of town right now. I love you.
沃德 其他人呢? 我們還沒設好警戒線
Ward, where is everyone? We haven't even set a perimeter.
我敢肯定 那個小混混一定看到魔杖了
I'm pretty certain that pee-wee gangster saw the Wand.
她怕得要命 她說有人要來
And she is spooked. Says somebody's coming.
好像是什麼壞傢伙要來了
Like... Like, someone bad.
怎麼...?
But what's...?
你看起來好像遇上了大麻煩
You seem like you-you have bigger troubles.
是你讓那個槍手跑掉的 對不對?
You let the shooter go, didn't you?
因為他也是獸人 有氏族血統?
'Cause he was clan blood?
你確定現在要跟我談這個?
Now? You wanna fucking go through this right now?
你還撒了什麼謊 豬頭?
What else you lie about, pigface?
你他媽的別碰我
Don't put your fucking hands on me!
你把我害慘了
You fucked me.
你把我們都害慘了
You fucked us both.
你這個豬頭混帳
Pigskin piece of shit.
你為了一個獸人 把我一輩子都搞砸了
You fucked my whole life over some stupid Orc knucklehead.
你去死吧 沃德
Fuck you, Ward.
滾開
Fuck off.
- 什麼．．．
- 你有種就掏槍啊
- What...? - I dare you.
有種你就給我拔槍
I dare you to pull your gun. Please.
來啊
Go ahead.
跟我槍戰 你死定了
I will fuck you up in a gunfight.
我給了你很多機會 讓你說實話
I gave you plenty of time to talk about this shit.
- 天網恢恢這下報應來了
- 是我放他走的
- Karma is a bitch, and here it come. - I let him go.
所以我們打算怎樣?
So what's the real plan?
今晚死兩個警察
Two cops die tonight.
那個精靈怎麼處理?
What about the Elf?
我會殺了她
I'll kill her.
- 行嗎？
- 行
- You good? - Yes, sir.
- 好的
- 警長
- Yeah. - Sarge?
你看到我的獠牙嗎? 它們被磨掉了
You see my teeth? They're filed.
我沒受血禮 我爸沒受血禮 我的爺爺也沒受血禮
I'm not blooded, my father's not blooded, his father's not blooded.
我這輩子受盡同族人的羞辱
I've been shit on by Orcs my whole fucking life.
你知道被自己族人唾棄 是怎樣的一種感覺麼?
Huh? You know what that feels like, when your own people hate you?
你為什麼要說謊?
Why'd you lie, Nick?
跟什麼氏族血統無關
It wasn't clan politics.
我只是抓錯了人
I just had the wrong guy.
那你來解釋一下?
Story time?
開槍射你的那個人 混入人群 我跟丟了他
The guy that shot you, I lost him in the crowd.
繞了一圈 我以為我逮住他了
I circled back, and I thought I had that fucking guy dead to rights.
但那只是另一個小鬼 他只是在塗鴉而已
But it was a different kid. He was just tagging.
其他警察也快到了
And the troops are coming.
一群沖昏頭的人類拿著槍 要找槍擊警察的獸人
Jacked-up humans with guns looking for an Orc who'd shot a cop.
你覺得那孩子還能活命麼?
You think that kid had a chance?
快走!
Go, go, go!
他們肯定當場斃了他 所以我做了正確的選擇 放他走了
They would've dropped him on the spot, so I did the right thing.
- 四級事態
- 安全
- Code four. - Clear.
你又沒看到他的臉 怎麼知道他不是開槍打我的那個人?
You never saw his face. How'd you know it wasn't the motherfucker that shot me?
因為他的氣味
His fucking smell.
進化並沒有我們喪失嗅覺能力
Yeah, years of evolution haven't taken away our sense of smell.
他聞起來不一樣
And he smelled different.
- 有哪個人類的陪審團會相信我說的這些話麼？
- 他是噴了體香劑嗎？
- What human jury would believe me? - What, he have Axe body spray?
你看 他們也會用你這種鳥話質疑我
Yeah, see, this is what I have to fucking deal with.
開槍射你的獸人
The Orc that shot you...
- 逃了
- 沃德！
- got away. - Ward!
時間到了
It's time.
時間...到了?
"It's... time"?
什麼時間?
Time for... Time for what?
他們四個都在?
All four of 'em standing there?
- 對
- 從你的左邊數起都是誰？
- Yeah. - Your left to right, who is it?
布朗 希克斯 伯拉德和程 怎麼了 沃德?
Brown, Hicks, Pollard, and Ching. What's going on, Ward?
不...不要...
Don't, don't, don't, don't...
不要
Don't.
搭檔 不要!
Partner, no!
放下槍 否則我打死你
Drop it, or I will fucking kill you.
聽我說
Hey, listen to me.
你不是這樣的人
This isn't like you.
好了 冷靜點
All right, calm down.
- 我知道這看起來挺糟的
- 閉嘴讓我看到你的雙手
- I know it looks bad. - Shut up. Shut up, show me your hands.
- 我別無選擇
- 閉嘴
- I didn't have a choice, Nick. - Shut up.
轉過身去
Now turn back around!
你有什麼計劃?
What's your plan?
我...
I'm...
我要逮捕你 所以給我閉嘴!
I'm gonna arrest you, so... so shut up!
首先 別再叫我閉嘴
First of all, stop telling me to shut up.
第二 你給我閉嘴
Second, I need you to shut up
- 好好聽我說
- 閉嘴！
- and listen to me. - Shut up!
轉過身去 跪下!
Turn around! Get on your fucking knees!
你想把我銬上 除非你先殺了我
Gonna have to fuckin' kill me if you think you're gonna put me in handcuffs.
沃德
Ward...
３Ａ９小隊報告
Three-Adam-9.
現場有四位警員倒下 其中一人昏迷 還有呼吸
I got four officers down, one officer conscious and breathing.
三位警員
Three officers...
殉職
KMA.
各小隊 有警員需要幫助 亞布罕街341號
All units, officer needs help, 341 Abrams.
有警員需要幫助 亞布罕街341號
Officer needs help, 341 Abrams.
- 收到
- 這真是糟透了
- Roger on the RA. - Oh, this is bad.
糟透了
This is so bad.
你別慌
Put your big girl panties on.
他們本來打算殺了我們 偷走魔杖
They were gonna kill us... over that Wand, all right?
他們瘋掉了
They were acting crazy.
別說話 別告訴任何人
Don't you say a word. Not to me, not to anybody.
雅各比 這些人是誰?
Jakoby? Jakoby, who are these people?
讓她上車
Oh, shit. Put her in the truck. Put her in the truck.
保護魔杖
Keep the Wand safe!
你們想怎樣?
Motherfucker, what?
保護魔杖
Protect the Wand.
那幾位警察...他們還好嗎?
Those cops there... they okay?
他們流了很多血啊 夥計
That's a lot of blood, homes.
那不關你的事
That ain't none of your concern.
你該去替他們做一下人工呼吸
Maybe you should go over and give 'em a little mouth-to-mouth. Huh?
這是犯案現場
This is an active crime scene.
我們沒有過節 你們回家吧
We ain't never had no beef, Poison. Why don't you take your people home.
我聽說 這埵酗@根魔杖
Word on the street, there's a Wand in this hood.
在哪呢 夥計
Where's it at, man?
- 這是我的地盤
- 我們是阿爾塔米拉幫的
- My hood. - Altamira.
大名鼎鼎的阿爾塔米拉幫
Alta-fucking-mira, eh?
沒錯
That's right.
所以我的小兄弟告訴我 有一群警察在我的地盤
So, when the little homies tell that the cops are shooting each other
自相殘殺
in my hood...
我就很好奇
makes me wonder. Hmm?
魔杖在哪?
Where's the Wand?
那只是謠傳
Ghetto rumors, homie.
你不想為了謠傳吃子彈吧?
Don't wanna get shot in your face over a rumor, do you?
你們回家吧
Why don't you go head home?
魔杖是屬於人民的
The Wand belongs to the people.
- 屬於貧民窟的人民
- 退後點
- To the barrio. - Get back!
兄弟
Homeboy.
- 聽好了
- 是的
- You heard me. - Smooth.
是我的
It's mine...
我殺光洛杉磯所有警察也要拿到魔杖
if I have to kill every fucking cop in LA.
你來試試啊 特警隊還有90秒就到
You're gonna get your chance, 'cause SWAT is about 90 seconds out.
尼克 上車
Nick, get in the truck.
快他媽的上車去
Get in the fucking truck, Nick!
- 聽主人的話快上車去
- 你去死吧
- Listen to your master. Get in the truck. - Fuck you.
- 去死的是你
- 你去死
- Fuck you, homie. - Fuck you.
怎麼了 你把狗狗染黑了?
What is that, a fuckin' Labradoodle you dipped in ink?
- 跟小豬亂搞麼夥計
- 醜得要命的混蛋
- Messed with puerco, homie. - Fucking ugly-ass motherfucker.
我看他就像豬
Looks like a puerco to me.
把魔杖拿給我
Get me that Wand.
把窗關上 防彈玻璃
Windows up, bulletproof.
- 特警隊要來嗎？
- 沒有尼克快開車！
- Is a SWAT team coming? - No, Nick. Go. Go!
- 方向錯了
- 車上有人趴著呢
- Wrong way, Nick. - Yeah, well, someone was on the car.
給我回來 狗娘養的!
Come back, you motherfucker!
防彈玻璃 笨蛋
Bulletproof, dickhead.
快!...
Go, go, go, go!
我們快走 能開多快開多快
Let's get the fuck outta here. Drive like you stole it.
阿爾塔米拉幫的兄弟們 我們去追這混蛋
Altamira gang, homie. Let's get these motherfuckers.
快!...
Go! Go!
往前開 不要側著開
Drive straight, not sideways!
媽的 我沒子彈了
Shit, I'm out.
- 該死的
- 你這笨手笨腳的
- Shit. - Butterfingers.
我們剛剛還那麼順利
We were doing so good.
警校堨i不會教這個
They don't teach that at the academy.
確實不會
No, they do not.
我們要回頭 把車停下 煉獄幫
We have to turn back. Stop the car. Inferni!
- 是煉獄幫
- 冷靜點
- Inferni! Inferni! - Relax, relax.
- 她說什麼呢
- 她不會罷休的
- The hell is she saying? - She won't let it go!
該死的!
Oh, shit!
發生什麼事了?
What's happening? Hey!
閉嘴!這是什麼東西?
Hey, shut up! Shut up! What is that?
閉嘴!
Shut up!
- 什麼東西？
- 有問題嗎？
- The fuck? - Problem?
技術部監聽到一些手機通話...
Tech services is flagging some weird-ass cell phone inter...
提到了魔杖
Talking about a Magic Wand.
救命 救我
Help me. Help.
娜莉卡
Larika.
莉拉 那個叛徒逃了
Leilah. The traitor escaped.
她拿了你的魔杖
She has your Wand.
我的眼睛濺到血了 我們撞到什麼了?
I got blood in my eye. What the fuck did we hit?
那是魔杖
Oh, that was the Wand.
你知道捆綁咒麼?
You know what a binding spell is?
這種法術會阻止魔杖遠離它的主人
It stops it from getting too far away from its owner.
會把魔杖拉回去
Pulls it back.
主人? 魔杖還有主人的?
Owner? Who owns a Wand?
光靈啊
A Bright.
求求你 先生
Please, sir.
告訴我 發生了什麼事
Tell me what happened.
告訴我
Tell me.
一堆警察開槍互相射擊
Cops started shooting at each other,
然後黑人警察殺光了他們
and a black cop killed them all.
他帶著一個獸人警察和精靈女孩逃走了
He left with an Orc cop and an Elf girl.
精靈女孩
An Elf?
不要
No! No!
聽著 你要冷靜一點
Okay, you know what? You need to sit your crazy ass down.
我們警局的警員 有一半都守舊得要命
Look, half of our division is on some old-school Rampart shit, a'ight?
他們打算先殺了你 再殺我
They're gonna kill you first, then they're gonna kill me,
然後把魔杖據為己有
they're gonna take the Wand,
然後就要闖下一連串大禍了
and that's when the stupid shit's gonna start.
要是在他們手媮棳潀n的 幫要是魔杖落到幫派分子手
And by the way, that's only if the gangstas don't get it first.
闖下的大禍數量要翻三倍
And that's when the triple stupid shit's gonna start.
我們要離開這個區
We gotta get out of this neighborhood.
不行 魔杖會阻止我們 捆綁咒會阻止我們
Yeah, but the Wand is gonna stop us. The binding spell is gonna stop us.
好吧 我們把魔杖藏起來
We'll hide the Wand.
藏在這 然後再回來拿
We'll hide it here and come back and get it.
我不會丟下魔杖
I am not abandoning the Wand.
- 我們不是管魔杖的警察
- 你想看到屍橫遍野嗎？
- We are not the fucking Wand police. - You want bodies on the street? Huh?
整個洛杉磯陷入一片火海
All of LA on fire?
這玩意太強悍了 基本上可以實現任何願望
This is like a nuclear weapon that grants wishes.
不行 聯邦調查局
No. The feds have people
有負責處理魔法的探員
that deal with magic.
- 我們聯繫上他們請求他們．．
- 你要去聯繫聯邦探員？
- We call them. We ask... - You wanna call the feds?
我射死了好幾個警員 記得嗎?
I got bodies on my gun, remember?
別看我 我還放走了一個獸人呢
Yeah, well, don't look at me, I just let an Orc go.
真的? 尼克?
Really, Nick?
真的?
Really?
這只是諷刺而已
That was irony.
不是說我真的放走了那個槍手
- No, that's just being an asshole. - Oh.
我們可以打給羅德古茲 他是縣治安官 不歸洛杉磯警局管
Gonna call Rodriguez. He's a sheriff, he's not LAPD.
- 他很可靠我們可以相信他
- 這是個好主意
- He's solid as fuck. We can trust him. - That's a good idea.
他們要來搶魔杖了
- They're coming for the Wand. - Ah, shit.
- 怎麼了？
- 鎖
- What is it? - The lock.
我們把鎖留在外面地上了 快去
We left the lock outside on the ground. Go.
搭檔 小心!
Partner, look out!
快來!快點!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
快走 快走
Let's go! Let's go!
尼克 我們走
Nick, let's go.
快點 快走
Come on, let's go!
你有毛病麼
What is your problem?
我把魔杖掉在地上了
Wait! I dropped the Wand.
別碰!
Don't you fucking touch that!
他們去哪了?
Where did they all go?
我們大概在呼吸他們化成的粉末了
I think we're breathing 'em.
- 幫我一個忙
- 嗯？
- Hey, do me a favor. - Uh-huh?
別再亂丟魔杖了
Don't drop that shit no more.
你說啥 不會
What? No.
我怎麼會亂丟?
Why would I?
- 阿爾塔米拉！
- 該死的！
- Altamira - Ah, shit! Ah!
沃德
Ward...
我開槍打死了一個人類 你看見了麼
I shot a human. Did you see?
我待會去買冰淇淋獎勵給你 該死的
Yeah, I'll get you some ice cream later. Damn.
- 我中彈了
- 你說什麼？
- I'm hit. - What?
他們不會罷休的 只會沒完沒了的衝過來 我們走吧
They're not gonna stop. They're gonna keep coming. Let's go.
你來這媟F嘛?
What are you doing here?
你這個他媽的叛徒
You fucking traitor.
繼續走啊
Keep walking.
媞卡!
Tikka!
媞卡在哪?
Where's Tikka?
媞卡!
Tikka!
背對背!靠在我背後!
On my back! Get on my back!
宰掉那些臭條子
Get those fucking cops.
媞卡!
Tikka!
沃德?
Ward?
沃德
Ward!
想嘗嘗子彈麼?
You want some of this?
找到媞卡了 走吧!
I found Tikka. Let's go!
媞卡!下來!
Tikka! Get down!
沃德 這邊!
Ward, this way!
- 開始行動
- 是長官
- Execute. - Sir.
- 快點！上！
- 已確認有人使用魔法
- Move! Let's go! Move! - Confirmed use of magic.
她是煉獄黨的人
She's Inferni.
真是一團糟
What a shitshow.
你願意解釋一下給我聽麼 長官?
You want to, uh, unpack this for me, boss?
莉拉
Leilah.
莉拉來過這
Leilah was here.
你在說什麼?
What are you talking about?
有人派她來殺掉媞卡
She was sent to kill Tikka,
- 然後媞卡把她變成那樣
- 她想要回她的魔杖
- then Tikka did that. - She wants her Wand back, right?
- 沒錯
- 然後媞卡拿到了魔杖
- Yes. - And Tikka has it.
- 對
- 跟她一起溜掉的警察．．．
- Yes. - And those cops she ran off with, uh...
沃德和...
Ward and...
怎麼? 雅各比
What? Jakoby.
我們在警局見過的那個獸人
The Orc cop we saw at the station.
他們根本不知道媞卡是誰
They have no idea who Tikka is.
已經20年了
It's been 20 years.
什麼已經20年了?
What does that even mean?
我追捕莉拉20年了
Twenty years I've been hunting Leilah.
現在她丟了魔杖
Without her Wand...
她很脆弱 我們就有機可乘了
she's vulnerable.
沃德 現在可不是購物的好時候啊
Now's a bad time to go shopping, Ward.
很多人都在追捕兩位警察 我們要換身衣服
Everybody's looking for two cops. We gotta switch it up.
說得對
Oh, yeah.
闖進霧牙幫的派對 對警民關係可沒什麼幫助
Running through a Fogteeth party is not good community policing.
我們還沒死 而且魔杖還在
Yeah, well, we're alive, and we got the Wand.
我只是說 獸人很記仇的
Orcs hold grudges. That's all I'm saying.
這還要你說 跟我來 我們走
Tell me about it. Hey, follow me. Let's go.
媞卡
Tikka.
- 謝謝你女士
- 快走
- Oh, thank you, ma'am. - Go.
- 不錯
- 謝謝
- That's good. - Thank you.
帶上你的女伴 趕快滾吧 快點
Take your old lady, get the fuck outta here. Go. Go.
我要你馬上離開這 明白了麼 快點
I need you to get the fuck outta here. All right? Go.
天哪
Jesus.
右邊有七個拿著砍刀 左邊有五個
Seven dudes with choppers down the right, five down the left.
中間有一堆王八蛋
Bunch of motherfuckers in the middle.
沃德警官
Officer Ward...
我覺得 我們該好好談談了
I think we need to talk.
毒男 你過的還好麼
Hey, Poison, how you doing?
今天晚上動靜鬧得很大
Some fucked-up shit went down tonight.
我的兄弟們想要你們的人頭 警察想要你們的人頭
My homies wanna cut your fucking head off, the cops wanna cut your fucking head off,
霧牙幫也想要你們的人頭
the Fogteeth gang wanna cut your fucking head off.
對 我就是有這麼大的魅力
Yeah, I got that effect on people, Poison.
可把我老婆給迷死了
Imagine how my old lady feels.
我嘛 我是想保護你的
Me? I just wanna protect you.
讓你安全回家 整件事一筆勾銷
Get you home safe and sound, with all your sins forgiven.
但是你得把魔杖給我
But you gotta give me that Wand.
你想做好事麼?
You wanna do the right thing?
讓我能用自己的雙腿行走
Help me walk again.
讓我能跟我老婆做愛
Help me make love to my old lady again.
讓我擺脫這個狗屁輪椅
Help me get rid of this shit again.
把魔杖給我 否則我會把這棟房子的所有出口封上
Give me the fucking Wand, or I will nail every door in this place shut
然後把這個地方燒成灰燼
and burn this place down to the fucking ground.
然後我會從灰燼中撿起魔杖 放聲大笑
And then I will pick up the Wand from the ashes, and I will laugh.
我跟我兄弟商量一下
Chopping it up with the homie for a sec, Poison.
我快沒耐心了 沃德警官
I'm running out of patience, Officer Ward.
- 我們把魔杖給他
- 你說什麼？
- Let's give this motherfucker the Wand. - What?
聽著 就算我們拉著這堛漫狾酗H給我們陪葬
Look, we gonna get everybody in here killed,
到最後他還是會得到魔杖
and then he's gonna take the damn Wand anyway.
我才不會把魔杖給他
I'm not giving that guy the Wand.
讓他到我的屍體上來取魔杖
Over my dead body.
他得先殺了我再說
He's gonna have to kill me first.
所以你這是願意在槍戰中喪命
So you wanna die in a gunfight
願意死在這個狗屁脫衣舞酒吧?
in a nasty-ass titty bar?
你是想這樣死去麼
That's what you want?
我不想死啊
I don't wanna die anywhere.
我想死 動手吧 我們自尋死路吧 現在就開干
You know what? Now I do. Fuck it. I wanna die. Let's do it right now.
我們在脫衣舞酒吧媞j戰至死
We gonna titty-bar-gunfight die.
我們馬上動手 準備好了?
Let's do it right here, right now. Ready?
我希望你槍打的准一些
I just wish your dumb ass was a better shot.
- 她說什麼？
- 她說惡魔要來了
- What she say? - She says the devil is coming.
那個惡魔就在外面 坐在輪椅
The devil's ass is out there in that wheelchair.
- 上吧我數到三就上一．．
- 干死他們
- Let's go. On three. One... - Let's do it.
- ．．．二．．．三
- 上啊
- ...two... three. - Yeah.
他媽的
Oh, shit.
快點 快跑
Go, go, go!
快點!
Go! Go, go, go!
讓開!
Move!
快點！
- Go, go, go! - Go, go, go!
快點!
Hurry!
我們是洛杉磯警察!
LAPD!
- 我的天
- 她是何方神聖？
- Oh, fuck. Come on! - Who is she?
煉獄黨 她要奪回魔杖
Inferni! She wants her Wand.
快走!
Move!
過了今晚 我就當不成警察了吧?
I'm not a cop after tonight, am I?
對 我也一樣
No. Neither am I.
我覺得我們還是專注於
I think we should probably spend our time
- 想辦法活命吧
- 活命？
- just trying to survive this shit. - Survive?
警察就是我的一切
Being a cop is all I've got.
現在我還算得上一位警察 如果我今晚死了
Right now I'm still a cop, and if I die tonight,
那我永遠都是警察 我...
I'll be a cop forever. I'll be a...
我永遠都是英雄
I'll be a hero forever.
整個世界都不在乎你 你怎麼會願意為它送命?
Why the fuck do you wanna die for a world that doesn't give a shit about you?
很久以前 獸人族站錯了邊
Orcs chose the wrong side a long time ago
自那時起我們就一直飽受折磨 為此付出代價
and they've been paying for it ever since.
獸人們看到我
You know, when an Orc sees me...
他們覺得我是一個想變成人類的獸人
they see a man... a wannabee human.
而人類覺得我是一個野獸
When humans see me, they see an animal.
他們討厭我
They hate me.
他們不討厭你啦
They don't hate you.
我們能分辨出人類是喜歡 還是厭惡我們的
We know when people like us and when they don't.
沃德 就比如你
Like you, Ward.
你從那房子堨X來的時候 眼睛媞◇〞漱釩
When you came out of that house with pure hatred in your eyes.
純粹的...仇恨
Pure... hatred.
聽我說 我都跟你談過這個問題了
Look, I told you what that was, all right?
你怎麼不告訴我真相 你就告訴我你是要幫那個獸人孩子啊
Why didn't you tell me the truth about helping the Orc kid?
我不是說 說出真相就能起到什麼很大的作用
I'm not saying it would've changed...
但也有可能會帶來一些改變啊
anything, but, shit, it might have.
我糊塗了
I got confused.
人類的世界 一切都黑白分明
And with humans, you understand, everything is so definite.
就比如 你說一句話 突然就變成法律了
Like, you say something, and all of a sudden it's law,
駟馬難追
and you can't walk it back.
你得告訴我真相
You gotta tell me...
因為我是你的搭檔
if I'm supposed to be your partner.
我不管我們對外要怎麼說 但你得告訴我真相
I don't care what we'll say to them, but you gotta tell me the truth.
你不能騙我啊
You can't lie to me.
所以我得相信你 但是你可以不信我?
Oh, so I'm supposed to trust you when you don't trust me?
你說的也有道理
That's a good point.
你是個好警察
You're a good cop.
別人對你不太好 於是
And people are really hard on you, so...
你也對自己也不太好
you're really hard on yourself.
別這樣 瘋婆子
Come on, crazy.
沃德 你知道麼 你是我的偶像
Ward, do you know that you are who I wish I was?
你無所畏懼
You're fearless.
無論發生什麼 你總是會有對策
You always know what to do.
你今天晚上所做的這些
What you did tonight,
獸人就是要那樣子才能受血禮
that's what it takes for an Orc to get blooded.
你的舉動充滿勇氣
An act of great bravery.
對我來說 你就是一個 受了血禮的人類
To me, you're like a blooded human.
我以前也像你這樣
I used to be like you.
以為自己能拯救所有人 解決所有問題
Think you can save everybody and fix everything and...
現在 我只是假裝自己是個好人
Now I just pretend to be a good dude.
你真的是個好人
You still are one.
我們是朋友嗎?
Are we friends?
不是 尼克 我們不是朋友 夥計
Nah, Nick. We're not friends, man.
你不想要我這種朋友
You don't want me as a friend.
把你的雙手舉起來 沃德
Show me your fucking hands, Ward.
羅德古茲 你在幹什麼呢?
Whoa, Rodriguez, what are you doing?
把你的雙手舉起來
Show me your fucking hands.
- 嘿是我叫你來的
- 把你的雙手舉起來
- Hey! I called you. - Show me your fucking hands.
- 你也是他們一夥的麼? - 什麼一夥的?- Are you a part of this? - Part of what?
我聽到對講機上 有人說你殺了一堆警察
All I know is I heard chatter on the radio saying you killed a bunch of cops.
- 把槍放下聽我說
- 閉嘴
- Put your gun down. Listen, the guys... - Shut the fuck up.
- 嘿
- 你把槍丟掉
- Hey! - Yo! Drop the weapon.
- 別動好了冷靜點
- 放下槍
- Tikka, stop. All right. Relax. - Drop the fucking weapon!
馬上丟掉
Drop it now!
- 羅德古茲聽我說
- 從槍旁邊走開
- Rodriguez. Listen to me. - Get away from the gun!
聽我說!
Listen!
跟我們一個組的警察們 想殺掉我們 拿走魔杖
The guys on our watch tried to do us over a Wand.
我們手上有魔杖
We have a Wand.
我們有一根貨真價實的魔杖
We have a Magic Wand.
- 行啊把魔杖給我看
- 別給他看
- All right, show me the Wand. - Don't show him shit.
- 他會殺掉我們然後據為己有
- 動作慢點
- He's gonna shoot us and take it. - Slow.
雅各比
Jakoby!
該死的
Shit.
我們首先要確保 那玩意不會落到壞人手
Okay, first thing we gotta do is keep that away from the bad guys.
- 我要打個電話先放下魔杖
- 行吧
- I'm gonna make a phone call. Put it down. - All right.
- 放下退後
- 羅德古茲
- Put it down. Now step back! - Rodriguez...
退後 什麼鬼? 她是個精靈?
Step the... God damn it! What the fuck? Is that an Elf?
- 羅德古茲
- 給我退後
- Rodriguez, put the phone down. - Step the fuck back!
- 把電話放下
- 我要打給聯邦探員
- Put your phone down. - I'm calling the feds.
- 我們應該這樣做的
- 聽我說
- It's what we're supposed to do. - Listen to me.
- 你冷靜點
- 聽我說我們不知道那邊是不是有內鬼
- Chill. Chill. Chill. - Listen. We don't know who's dirty.
- 羅德古茲掛掉電話
- 你閉嘴
- Rodriguez, put the phone down. - Shut the fuck up.
- 把電話放下．．．
- 等一下
- Put the phone do... - Hold on!
你不能告訴他們
Don't tell 'em shit.
有個警官說找到了魔杖
I got a deputy claiming to have the Wand.
對
Yes?
他們問我們目前在哪
They wanna know where we're at.
把電話給我
Give me the phone.
你是誰?
Who is this?
你又是誰呢?
Who's this?
我是他媽的拿著魔杖的人
The motherfucker with the Wand.
是你打給我們的 你在哪?
You called us. Where are you?
聽著
All right, look...
魔杖在我手上 我有幾點要求
I got the Wand, but I need something.
- 你要特赦
- 如果我給你魔杖
- You need forgiveness. - If I give you this Wand.
舉個例子
And let's just say...
可能會有人指證我
I don't know, somebody accused me of, uh, some dumb shit, like...
說我殺了一堆警察之類的
killing a bunch of cops.
你這種當官的 應該有辦法解決這種問題吧?
A man like you could fix that shit, right?
如果你是防止魔法武器 落入某些 比如腐敗分子手中
If you were protecting a weapon of magic from, let's say, corrupt individuals...
當然不會有任何針對你的指控
there would be no charges.
沒錯 現在就是這種情況
That's exactly what happened.
我就問你
Hypothetically.
你應該可以擺平那些事吧
A man like you could dead that noise, right?
- 女精靈跟你在一起嗎？
- 對
- Do you have the Elf girl? - Yeah.
- 我們只能把信號範圍縮小至幾個街區內
- 行
- Can only narrow it down to a few blocks. - Okay.
來吧 我們走! 出發!
Come on, let's go! Move out! Move out!
- 信號斷掉了
- 該死的
- The phone died. - Shit.
- 好吧聽我說
- 不等一下等一下
- All right, look... - Okay. No, hold the... Hold the fuck up.
- 羅德古茲
- 把你搭檔銬上
- Hey, Rodriguez... - Have to cuff your partner.
- 不用給任何人銬上手銬
- 看起來情況很糟啊
- Nobody's handcuffing anybody. - It doesn't look good.
現場他媽的有一個獸人 然後一堆警察死掉了?
A fucking Orc and a bunch of dead cops?
你這是什麼意思?
All right. What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
夥計 我跟你說實話
I'm just being real with you, man.
他們認定是雅各比干的
They want it to be Jakoby.
不管是不是他幹的 他也難逃其咎
Okay? Whether it's him or not.
如果聯邦探員到了 發現咱們沒把他被銬起來
If he's not cuffed by the time they get here,
肯定會把你們兩個都斃了
they're gonna smoke both of you motherfuckers.
- 把他銬起來吧
- 別爭了
- Cuff your partner. - Don't...
- 沃德沒關係的
- 別那樣跟我說話
- Ward, it's okay. - Don't reach on me like that.
我們不能就這麼逃下去
We can't run all night.
就這麼幹吧
Let's do it.
是時候了結這一切了
It's time to end this.
給我銬上吧
Let's go in.
把我的槍拿走
Take my gun.
轉過身去
Turn around.
嘿 沃德
Hey, Ward...
我不能坐牢
I can't go to prison.
他們會把我的皮都給扒了
They'll skin me alive.
你不會坐牢的 你是清白的
You're not going to jail. You didn't do shit.
那些人都是我殺的
I shot everybody.
沃德 閉嘴吧你 找個律師
Ward, shut the fuck up and lawyer up.
進去!...快點!
Get inside! Get inside! Go!
媽的 那是什麼情況?
Shit. What was that?
好女孩 幫我把鎖打開 你有看到什麼嗎?
Good girl. Let me out. Let me out. You see anything?
- 不什麼都沒看到
- 先生請離窗戶遠點
- No, I can't see anything. - Sir, get away from that window!
糟了 快跑
Oh, shit! Move! Come on!
叛徒
Traitor.
該死的
Oh, shit, shit.
拉我出去
Get me out. Get me out.
拉我出去!
Get me out!
我的天
Oh, God.
該死的
Oh, shit.
我就說嘛 獸人會記仇
I told you Orcs hold grudges. Huh? What'd I say?
聽著 你們魯莽駕駛 今天放你們一馬
All right, look. I'm gonna cut you a break on the reckless driving.
你們現在回到車上 安全開回家
But I need you to return to your vehicles and drive home safely.
我要你趕緊扭著你的那個丑屁股
So I need you to take your fat Shrek-looking ass
坐回車子 開車回家找你老婆
back to your vehicle and drive the fuck home to Fiona. A'ight?
- 你想要坐牢嗎？
- 找老婆
- Do you wanna go to jail? - Fiona?
用獸人語跟這幫混蛋講
Tell these dickheads in Orkish
叫他們滾回車上 開車回家
to get the fuck back in their vehicles and drive home,
- 否則全部都要坐牢
- 但是．．．他們都聽得懂英語啊
- or they're all going to jail. - But... they speak English.
你們聽得懂吧? 會講英語吧?
But... You understand, right? Speak English?
是啊 當然
Yeah. Of course.
把他帶去教堂
Take 'em to the church!
你知道麼
You know...
我不是來自這堛
I'm not from here.
我在邁阿密長大
I grew up in Miami.
那堛疑~人社區很不錯 很強大
Great Orc communities there, strong Orc communities.
我們會跟矮人和人類一起 在街上搞派對
We'd have block parties with dwarves and humans.
很好玩的 夥計
It was fucking fun, man.
我當時沒上黑道
I wasn't in the game then.
我當時是個公交車司機
I was a bus driver.
然後我搬到洛杉磯
Then I moved to LA.
他媽的天使之城啊
Fucking City of Angels, right?
聽著 我跟你說話的時候
Listen, I would really appreciate it
你得看著我 這是基本的尊重
if you gave me the respect of looking at me when I'm talking to you.
我來到這 看到的是腐敗的官僚系統
I get here and I see how broke the system is.
獸人們牽扯在警察和黑幫之間
Orcs caught between the police and the gangsters.
精靈搾取我們的錢
Elves making money off us.
- 於是我就組建了．．．
- 媞卡
- So I organize... - Tikka.
我的社區
...my community.
我們自成一派了
We got our own thing now.
每個月...
Every month...
- 看著我混蛋
- 對不起
- Look at me, motherfucker. - Sorry.
每個月
Every month...
我都會搞一場派對
I throw a big party.
讓大家喝醉吃飽
Get everyone drunk, feed 'em.
不分種族
All races...
所有人一起玩 只有一個規則
partying together, with one rule.
不能帶槍
No guns.
這麼多年 都相安無事
After years of peace...
誰壞了規矩 把槍帶進來了?
who brings in the guns?
是我們
We did, yeah.
- 來惹禍的是誰？
- 是我們
- The drama? - Us.
踐踏我們慶典的是誰?
Disrespects our celebration?
他媽的警察!
The motherfucking police!
未受血禮的獸人
An unblooded Orc.
跟著人類長大 從來沒有人舉手向他致敬
Grew up with humans. Never had a hand raised for him in respect.
他這是在說什麼呢?
What's he saying?
- 假裝自己是個好人
- 都是些老生常談的話
- Playing the nice guy. - Nothing I haven't heard before.
你的這位人類朋友很高興 能炫耀自己有個獸人朋友
Your buddy's so happy to say he's got a Orc friend.
媽的 我也不想跟他一起的
Shit. I'm stuck with this motherfucker.
- 你不是認真的？
- 隨口說說而已
- Seriously? - I'm just saying,
反正我們也沒有一起去過夜店之類的
ain't like we's stomping through the club together.
沃德
Ward.
魔杖在哪?
Where is the Wand?
什麼魔杖?
What Wand?
- 聽著兄弟我們是一家人
- 尼克
- Hey, man, we're family. - Hey, Nick.
他只是想操控你 別讓他得逞
He's just trying to get in your head. Don't let him in your head.
我不是要操控他 我們的靈魂是共通的
I'm not trying to get in his head, man. I'm in his soul.
我們是同族人
We're the same thing.
- 我告訴你魔杖在哪
- 好啊
- I'll tell you where the Wand is. - Yeah?
插在你屁眼堣F
It's up your fucking ass.
魔杖在哪?
Where's the Wand?
揍這兩個混蛋
Whip these motherfuckers.
教訓他們
Get them!
別傷害他們
Don't hurt 'em.
你這娘炮
Pussy.
鈍牙齒
Roundtooth.
假獸人
False Orc.
未受血禮的懦夫
Unblooded coward.
魔杖在哪?
Where is the Wand?
什麼魔杖?
What... What Wand?
你這個混蛋!
You motherfucking dickhead!
魔杖在哪?
Where is the Wand?
什麼魔杖?
What Wa... Wand?
根本就沒有魔杖!
There's no Wand!
阿爾塔米拉幫就認為有魔杖
Altamira thinks there's a Wand.
警察也認為有魔杖
The police think there's a Wand.
聯邦探員們也認為有魔杖
The feds think there's a Wand.
我覺得魔杖是有的!
I think there's a Wand!
根本就沒有魔杖
There's no Wand.
只是貧民窟的傳說而已
Ghetto Fairy tales.
把那個精靈女人帶來
Bring me the Elf.
我會讓她的鮮血濺你一臉
I will cover you with her hot blood.
她與這事無關
She don't have shit to do with this.
魔杖在哪?
Where is the Wand?
我們是警...
We are police off...
察
officers.
你不能這樣對我們
And you can't do this to us.
殺掉他們
Kill them!
看著他們死吧 精靈
Watch your friends die, Elf.
你沒有屈服
You didn't break.
你應該接受血禮的
You deserve to be blooded.
你本來可以成為一個偉大的獸人
You would have made a great Orc.
我是一個好獸人
I am... a great Orc.
我兒子今晚就能受血禮了
My son earns his colors tonight.
麥克
Mikey.
再見了 搭檔
Bye, partner.
你在猶豫什麼?
Why are you waiting?
爸爸 我認得他
Father... I know him.
什麼?
Ward...
是他幫我逃脫警察追捕的
He helped me escape from the police.
我放走的
That's the guy...
就是他
that I let go.
他救了我一命 我不能殺他
He saved my life. I cannot kill him.
回家去吧
Go home.
離開這
You can't be here.
去你的 你這個綠鼻子的豬頭混帳
Fuck you, you green pig-nose piece of shit.
開槍啊
Shoot, bitch.
- 我要你求饒
- 開槍射我啊混蛋
- Beg for it! Beg! - Shoot me, bitch. Shoot, bitch!
去你媽的
Fuck you.
- 你要尊重我
- 去你的開槍啊
- Show your respect! - Fuck you! Do it! Shoot!
- 你開槍啊混蛋
- 你要尊重獸人受死吧
- Shoot, motherfucker! Bring it! - Give us respect! Here it comes!
他復活了 預言成真了
This is a Prophecy, for he has risen.
沃德?
Hey, hey.
發生什麼事了?
W-Ward? What happened?
沒什麼 怎麼了?
Uh... Nothing. Why?
肯定有事發生了 我感覺好極了
Well, something happened. I feel great.
不我們走吧快點
- Nah, just go, go, go. - Okay.
你是光靈
You're a Bright?
你他媽的是光靈
You're a fucking Bright?
要是我們之前被圍住的時候 就告訴我們 那多好
Would've been nice to know that when we was getting fucked up.
可以用魔法變一台直升機 然後逃走
Could've had a magic helicopter take us somewhere.
我的訓練剛剛開始
I only started my training.
我只認識幾個咒語而已
I only know a few spell words.
她英語說的也很流利了
She speaks English pretty good now, too.
- 現在我相信你了
- Now I trust you. - Um...
你要給我們一點福利啊
You gonna need to unfuck this, okay?
比如把我們送去泡溫泉之類的
A'ight? You gonna magic us to Palm Springs or some shit.
我救了你朋友一命
I saved your friend's life.
那還不夠嗎?
Isn't that enough?
這只是個開始 但是...
It's a start, but...
沃德 打住 有件事我覺得很重要
Uh, Ward, stop. I happen to think it's a pretty big deal.
謝謝你
Thank you.
媞卡 獵捕我們那些精靈 他們到底是誰?
Now, Tikka, who are these Elves who are hunting us?
他們要幫助魔君回歸...
They're aiding the return of the Dark Lord...
他會塗炭生靈
so he can slaughter billions
奴役倖存者 服侍他 迎來新的魔法紀元
and enslave the survivors to serve him in a new age of magic.
就這樣?
Oh. That's all.
都是一些光明會說的屁話
Just some Illuminati shit.
他們是煉獄黨的
They're Inferni.
一百年前他們就把光明會給摧毀了
They destroyed the Illuminati a hundred years ago.
你怎麼知道這些的?
How do you know all this?
我也是煉獄黨的
I, too, am Inferni.
但是我逃走了
But I escaped.
光明之盾把我藏起來
The Shield of Light hid me.
莉拉把她的魔杖借給一個刺客 派她來殺我
Leilah gave an assassin her Wand to kill me.
但是我從她手媟m走了魔杖
But I got the Wand from her.
讓魔杖離莉拉遠點
Keep it away from Leilah.
千萬不能讓她拿回魔杖
She mustn't get her Wand back.
莉拉能讓魔君恢復力量
With it, she can restore the Dark Lord to power.
那是什麼? 你臉上黑黑的是什麼東西?
Hey, what is that? What's the shit? What's the black stuff?
聽著...
Hey. Look... All right.
好吧等一下你別就這麼死了
All right, hey, look, don't-don't-don't check out on us.
別讓她拿到 別讓莉拉拿到魔杖
Keep it away from her. Keep the Wand away from Leilah.
- 答應我
- 我答應你
- Promise me. - Yes.
她需要醫生 我們要送她去急救室
All right. She needs medical attention. We gotta get her to an emergency room.
但怎麼去?
But how?
行了 走吧
Got it. Let's go!
快點
Go, go!
我們不會讓你死的
We won't let you die.
我們要怎麼救你
How do we save you?
只有光明之盾能救我
Only the Shield of Light can help me.
他們在哪?
Where are they?
在家
Home.
- 家
- 家？家在哪？
- Home. - Home? Where's home?
亞布罕街那?
Wait, home. Uh... the Abrams' house?
那堛漱H全死了
Everybody was dead there.
那埵陪茪籉
There's a pool.
水池互相連結
The pools are... connected like...
就像聖樹的根
the roots of a holy tree.
沃德 她撐不住了 我們得送她回去
Ward, she's dying. We have to take her back to where we found her.
- 我們不能去那個房子
- 我們別無選擇
- No. We are not going back to that house. - Yes.
我們得去醫院 那埵麻憟
We're gonna get to the hospital. There's doctors there.
我們要把她和魔杖交給聯邦探員
We're gonna turn her and the Wand over to the feds.
- 沃德
- 我要讓我的人生回到正軌
- Ward. Ward. - I want my life back.
她讓我死而復生
She brought me back from the dead.
你別跟我談這個
Hey, don't kook out on me right now, all right?
我們還不知道當時究竟發生了什麼
We don't know exactly what happened.
你得接受這個奇跡
You have to accept the miracle.
- 我們不能回那個房子
- 我們兩個．．．都是普通人
- We're not going back to that house. - You and me are simple people.
沒什麼特別的
We mean nothing.
沒有人會歌頌我們
People don't write about us.
但你不明白麼 現在就像英雄時代一樣
But this, don't you see, is like a time of heroes?
吉拉克跟我一樣 也是個沒受血禮的獸人
Jirak was unblooded like me.
沒人正眼看他
An Orc that nobody cared about.
他...
He...
他一統了九族大軍 擊敗魔君
He united the Nine Armies, and they defeated the Dark Lord. He...
他是農民 卻改變了世界
He was a farmer who changed the world.
人們對他兵刃相向
They raised their blades to him.
在那個瞬間 他就受了血禮
He was blooded in that very moment.
他實現了偉大預言 沃德
He fulfilled a great Prophecy, Ward.
我們可能也身處預言之中
I think we might be in a Prophecy.
- 我們並沒有身處預言之中
- 你怎麼知道？
- We're not in a Prophecy, all right? - How do you know?
我們現在明明是身處一台偷來的豐田車
We're in a stolen Toyota Corolla.
- 不
- 好嗎？你看我的表情
- No. - Okay? Look at my face.
這個不是什麼「身處預言之中」的表情
All right? This is not a Prophecy face.
而是"這天晚上糟透了"的表情
This is a bad-night face.
行嗎? 我們要送她去醫院
Okay? And we're gonna get to the hospital,
聯邦探員會解決這一切的
and the feds are gonna put an end to it.
你給我閉嘴 沃德 聽我說
Shut the fuck up, Ward, and listen to me.
我們要回去
We have to go back.
我們前途一片迷茫
There's nothing ahead of us.
我的天 這些是聯邦探員的屍體啊
Ah, man. These guys are feds.
該死的
Oh, shit.
我拿了把大傢伙
I get the big gun.
我可不介意用這種大傢伙
I didn't mind having the big gun.
那個...那是個炸彈
That... That's a bomb.
沒錯
Yes, it is.
- 你要我拿著？
- 沒錯
- You want me to hold it? - Yes, I do.
為什麼?
W... Why?
以防萬一
You never know.
我坐在您跟前 黑暗之王
I sit before you, Lord of Darkness.
侍奉您是我的榮幸
Serving your will is my honor.
我會讓您回到這個世界
I will return you to this world.
他們來了!那邊!在牆壁!
They're coming! There! In the wall!
射穿牆壁!
Shoot through the wall!
沃德!
Ward!
尼克!
Nick!
快走!
Nick! Let's go!
雅各比
Jakoby!
我把炸彈給她了
I gave her the bomb.
以防萬一嘛
You never know.
往左劃
Swipe left.
糟了
Oh, shit.
開槍射她!
Shoot her!
尼克 開槍打她
Nick, will you please shoot her!
開槍! 開槍打她
Shoot! Shoot her!
幹得漂亮
Good work.
水 把我放在水
The water. Put me in the water.
嘿 行了 接下來的交給我
Hey. You're done. I got it from here.
現在要怎麼辦?
So what now?
要有信念
Have faith.
她來了
She's coming.
尼克!
Nick!
你到底是什麼東西?
The hell are you?
我是位戰士
I'm a warrior.
是女祭司 也是愛人
A priestess, a lover.
我的君王要什麼 我就是什麼
I am whatever my Lord needs me to be.
回來吧
Come home.
請你回來
Please, come home.
我不能回去
I can't go back.
跟我一起進入夢境吧
Dream with me again.
你所愛的一切 都是破敗不堪的
What you love is broken, rotten.
這個人類和那個獸人
This man and the Orc...
他們對你而言 有什麼意義?
...what are they to you?
- 他們是好人
- 不
- They're good. - No.
是時候回家了
It's time to come home.
- 太遲了我不能回家
- 是時候醒來了
- It's too late. I can't come home. - It's time to wake up.
別再說了 快殺了我!
So just shut up and kill me.
Just shut up and kill me!
- 你本性並非如此！
- 別說了快殺了我！
- This is not you! - Shut up and kill me!
你本性並非如此! 都是你幹的
This is not you! This is you!
你對我妹妹做了什麼?
What have you done to my sister?
你對她做了什麼?
What have you done to her? What did you do?
該死的
Shit.
尼克 如果你瞄準的是魔杖 那你射得很好
Nick, if you were aiming at the Wand, that was a really good shot.
但你要射她的頭!
But shoot her in her head!
這樣嗎?
Like this?
完了
I can't.
沒子彈了
I'm out.
不!
No!
你不是光靈
You're not a Bright.
你敢碰我的魔杖
You touch my Wand...
它會把你炸成碎片
and it will splatter you all over the walls.
我覺得這樣挺好的
I think that's kind of the plan.
咱們一起死
Think I'mma just kill us all.
沃德
Ward...
我覺得還是別那樣吧
I wouldn't do that.
沒事的
It's all right.
我們不是身處預言之中麼
We're in a Prophecy, right?
這不可能
This is impossible.
尼克 我拿到魔杖了
Hey, Nick, I got the Wand.
現在怎麼辦?
Um, what now?
也許...也許你是個光靈 沃德
Maybe you're a... You're a Bright, Ward.
使用魔杖啊!
Use it!
真是個好主意
Oh, good idea.
把魔杖給我...
Give it to me...
否則我就殺了她
or she dies.
Vykwarus.
那是攻擊的咒語
The war word is Vykwarus.
Vykwarus!
堶惘野靈
We got a Bright in there!
媞卡!
Tikka. Tikka.
- 媞卡！
- 沃德沒事了
- Tikka! - Ward! It's okay.
- 她．．．她滾進去了
- 別急沃德
- She just... She rolled in. - Come on, Ward!
- 她消失了沒事的
- 我不想傷害她的
- She's gone. It's okay. - I didn't hurt her.
- 媞卡！
- 沃德媞卡沒事的
- Tikka! - Ward, Tikka's okay.
她消失了
She's gone.
- 媞卡！
- 沃德想想你的女兒吧
- Tikka! - Ward, think of Sophia.
走吧 沃德
Come on, Ward!
獸人!
Orc!
別開槍
Stand down.
沃德!
Ward!
不要!
No!
達瑞!
Daryl!
你現在安全了
You're safe now.
沃德!
Ward!
達瑞!
Daryl!
沃德!
Ward!
我把你救出來了!
I know. I gotcha.
救出來了
Got him!
沃德!我們沒事了!
Ward! We made it!
我們出來了
We got out!
你沒事了
I got you. You're okay.
你還好嗎?
Are you okay?
快呼吸 沃德
Breathe, Ward.
說句話
Say something.
尼克 你看
Nick... look.
你還不是我的朋友
Still not my friend.
我也不怎麼喜歡你
I never really liked you anyway.
現在你受了血禮 就以為自己很了不起哦
Think you're a big dog now you're blooded, huh?
對 我是挺了不起的
Yeah, pretty big.
尼克
Hey, Nick.
怎麼了
Yeah.
去他媽的魔法
Fuck magic.
我還是覺得有點酷啦
Well, I don't know. I still think it's kinda cool.
你們怎樣?
How you doing, fellas?
- 還好嗎？
- 嘿
- Good? - Hey.
尼克 消防員來了
Nick, the firemen are here.
- 我們該去當消防員的
- 對
- We should've been firemen. - Yeah.
能給我片止痛藥嗎?
Hey, can I get a aspirin?
嘿 氏族兄弟
Hey, Clan Blood.
達瑞
Daryl.
Oh, Daryl.
你感覺如何?
How are you feeling?
還好嗎?
You feeling okay?
好吧
Uh, yeah.
好 我看懂了你的表情
Okay, I get it.
糟了
Oh, shit.
那可不太妙
Well, that can't be good.
是啊
Yeah.
怎麼沒把你銬起來?
Why you not locked up?
他們好像覺得你比我更危險
I think they think you're more dangerous than me.
嘿
Hey.
你什麼都別說
Don't say shit.
長官我們只是執行任務已
- Sir, we were just responding to a call. - Mmm.
我跟我搭檔 我們... 到處都是什麼魔法的玩意
My partner and I, we... But there was all this crazy magic stuff.
我是說 布朗和希克斯
I mean, everything that happened with Brown...
還有伯拉德和程他們．．．
- Hey, hey, hey. - ...and Hicks and Pollard and Ching...
- 他們要沃德警官殺我
- 嘿尼克
- They wanted Officer Ward to shoot me. - Hey. Nick.
他們要沃德殺我 然後偷走魔杖 知道麼?
They wanted to him to kill me so they could get the Wand, remember?
他不願意那樣做 因為他是好人
And he wouldn't do it 'cause he's a stand-up guy.
然後 他們說要殺我
He wouldn't do it. But then they said they would kill me, so he...
於是他只好採取行動
he had to take action,
- 開槍了
- 不對我印象中不是這樣的
- like, with his gun, right? - No. That's not my recollection.
尼克 你怎麼...
Hey, Nick, why don't you just...
你等一下
If you hold up a second...
- 怎樣？
- 等他們提問
- What? - ...they'll ask us questions.
事實就是這樣的 我發誓 我們只是執行任務而已
It's what happened, I swear to God. We just returned to the call.
但是這起事件中牽涉到的力量 超乎我們的想像
But there are forces at play that are beyond.
- 有個精靈女人
- 尼克
- There was, uh, an Elf woman. - Hey, Nick.
她是魔杖的主人 對吧?
She owned the Wand. Right?
她肯定是魔杖的主人 是個壞人 很會打扮 跟你一樣
It must've been hers. Not a nice lady. Dressed very well, but... Like you.
但她真的糟透了 她...
But she was a terrible woman. She...
- 她服侍魔君
- 尼克．．．
- Uh, she served the Dark Lord. - Nick...
- 我敢肯定
- 讓他們．．．
- I know it. - Let them...
- 讓他們提問
- 他們必須知道
- Let them ask us questions. - They need to know this.
- 他提問我們回答
- 然後有個天使
- Let him ask us questions. - There was an Angel.
然後黑幫的人就開始追我們
All right. That was then when the gangsters were chasing us.
- 情況不是這樣的
- 她叫媞卡
- Uh, the context is a little off. - Tikka.
媞卡
Oh, Tikka.
很可憐 她是個年輕的光靈
So sad. Tikka... Tikka was a young Bright.
她...
She... She... She...
她用魔杖救了我
She... She used the Wand and she saved my life.
我...我的靈魂脫離了身體 然後她讓我復活
I was... My soul was leaving my body, and she brought me back.
沃德警官?
Officer Ward?
我們接到報警電話 便出警 進行調查
We responded to a 415 disturbance call.
我們接近那住宅之後 發現那是一個...
Uh, upon approaching the residence, we realized that it was a safe house
- 極端分子的窩點
- 現場有很多奇怪的玩意
- for an extremist group. - Full of weird...
我們隨即遭遇襲擊
We immediately took fire,
於是請求增援
uh, at which point we called for backup.
然後...不幸地...
And... unfortunately...
- 有警員在槍戰中遇害
- 我沒看過那種槍法
- officers were killed in the exchange. - I've never seen shooting like it.
他轉過身 都沒瞄準
He turned around, sight unseen,
連開四槍 四個人應聲倒地
four of them, bang, bang, bang, bang. Dropped...
就好像是一顆子彈把他們四個都打死了
like it was one bullet.
不好意思 請繼續
Sorry, keep going.
緊接著黑幫成員到場
Gangsters showed up,
然後情況急轉直下
and it just went really sideways from that point.
如果你們聯邦探員沒出現...
And had you guys not shown up...
那後果不堪設想
it would've... it would've been really bad.
所以你們是真正的英雄
Uh, so the real heroes in this are you guys.
我們得謝謝你們
So we wanna say thank you.
尼克 快謝謝這些聯邦探員們
Nick, thank the nice federal agents.
謝謝你們
Thank you.
所以 我明確表示
So, let me say, unequivocally...
根本沒有魔杖
there was no Wand.
也沒有什麼魔法
And there was no magic.
只是兩個巡警
Just a couple of street cops...
做好本職工作而已
doing our job.
我明白這是什麼情況了
Oh, I know what this is.
所以情況就是這樣麼
Then that's what happened?
是的 長官 就是這樣
Yes, sir. That's exactly what happened.
你也是這麼覺得的吧
Yes?
對 我同意他的說法
No, I'm with him.
我在此明確表態了
Unequivocally.
面對著沉迷於遠古傳說的恐怖分子
Faced with armed terrorists obsessed with myths from thousands of years ago,
兩位警員與持槍歹徒英勇作戰
two of our officers held the line.
我真不想看到那些混蛋的照片跟羅德古茲放在一起
I hate seeing those scumbags up there with Rodriguez.
算了 沃德
Let it go, Ward.
我們心堛器D就行 那就夠了
We know, okay? That's enough.
達瑞·沃德警官 還有全國首位獸人警官 尼可拉斯·雅各比
Officer Daryl Ward, and our nation's first Orkish police officer, Nicholas Jakoby.
雅各比警官
Officer Jakoby.
恭喜沃德警官
Congratulations, Ward.